Railroad Case Files 5014
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Stenographer's Minutes for Docket No. Ex Parte 106 before the Interstate Commerce Commission Vol. 16, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  In re: The effect upon operation, service, and expenses of applying the principle of the six-hour day in the employment of railway employees
- Stenographer's Minutes for Docket No. Ex Parte 106 before the Interstate Commerce Commission Vol. 2, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Stenographer's Minutes for Docket No. Ex Parte 106 before the Interstate Commerce Commission Vol. 3, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Stenographer's Minutes for Docket No. Ex Parte 106 before the Interstate Commerce Commission Vol. 4, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Stenographer's Minutes for Docket No. Ex Parte 106 before the Interstate Commerce Commission Vol. 5, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Stenographer's Minutes for Docket No. Ex Parte 106 before the Interstate Commerce Commission Vol. 6, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Stenographer's Minutes for Docket No. Ex Parte 106 before the Interstate Commerce Commission Vol. 7, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Stenographer's Minutes for Docket No. Ex Parte 106 before the Interstate Commerce Commission Vol. 8, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Stenographer's Minutes for Docket No. Ex Parte 106 before the Interstate Commerce Commission Vol. 9, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Stenographer's Minutes for Docket No. Ex Parte 106 before the Interstate Commerce Commission Vol. 10, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Stenographer's Minutes for Docket No. Ex Parte 106 before the Interstate Commerce Commission Vol. 11, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Stenographer's Minutes for Docket No. Ex Parte 106 before the Interstate Commerce Commission Vol. 12, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Transcript of Proceedings of the National Mediation Board, National Railway Labor Emergency Board, No. l6h, Carriers Represented by National Railway Labor Conference and BLF&E, 1964, Volumes 3-9. (Box 16)
  - Stenographer's Minutes for Docket No. Ex Parte 106 before the Interstate Commerce Commission Vol. 13, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Stenographer's Minutes for Docket No. Ex Parte 106 before the Interstate Commerce Commission Vol. 14, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Stenographer's Minutes for Docket No. Ex Parte 106 before the Interstate Commerce Commission Vol. 15, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Stenographer's Minutes for Docket No. Ex Parte 106 before the Interstate Commerce Commission Vol. 1, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Before the Interstate Commerce Commission: Ex Parte 206, Increased Efficiency and Productivity in Maintenance of Way Work, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Before the President's Emergency Board: Third Diesel Case, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    Rebuttal: Employees' Exhibits 69,70,71 and 72 discipline
  - Proposed Changes in Wage Bases and in the Consist of Engine Crews, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Firemen's General Requests and Engineers' Diesel Requests
  - Statement of Daniel P. Loomis with respect to Explanation of Mountain and Desert Differentials, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Testimony of CM Buckley in the Third Diesel Case: Direct Examination, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Before the Emergency Board: Third Diesel Case, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Third Diesel Case: Rebuttal of Employee Exhibit 75-A-B-C-D, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Third Diesel Case: Testimony of James M. Symes, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Before the President's Emergency Board: Third Diesel Case, Rebuttal - Statement of LD Phillips, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Third Diesel Case: Rebuttal Exhibit Reply to Testimony of Employee's Witness RA Pike, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Third Diesel Case: Negotiation of the Firemen's Southeastern Diesel Agreement of May 11, 1944, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Third Diesel Case: Higher than Standard Rates Southeastern Territory, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Third Diesel Case: Carriers' Rebuttal, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    Carriers' Rebuttal Statements to Accident Investigations contained in Employees' Exhibit 75-A, B, C, and D
  - Third Diesel Case, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    Locomotives classified according to weight on drivers
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit 57, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    Excerpts from the record in the first diesel case (1943) relating to differing practices and rules in respect to the head brakeman in freight service
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 56, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    Casualties to firemen common to coal burning locomotives but which do not occur on oil burning locomotives; all railroads; years 1944 to 1948
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 55, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    Number of casualties to engineers and firemen in steam and electric locomotive operations
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 54, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    The adverse effect of the employment of additional firemen on the productivity of the railroad industry
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 52, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    Award No. 11644, First Division NRAB affirming right of carrier to have head brakeman call signals
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 51, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    Instructions to diesel crews: fireman remaining in cab while train in motion, head brakeman riding in cab of diesel locomotives
  - Third Diesel Case, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    Analysis of testimony of JL Shepard
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 50, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    Cost of proposals
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 49, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    Locomotive statistics
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 47, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    Earnings of firemen (helpers)
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 46, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    Standard basic rates for firemen (helpers)
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 45, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    Photographs of decks of coal burning and oil locomotives
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 43, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    Electric helper differential
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 42, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    History of electric engine service
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 41, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    Productivity and the establishment of firemen's wage bases
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 40, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    Data on practical aspects of mountain differential Shasta Division, Southern Pacific Company
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 37, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    History of the wage differential applicable to firemen assigned to oil burning locomotives
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 39, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    Data relating to oil burner differential
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 3, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    Appearances of carriers' conference committee and counsel
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 4, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    The issues before the board
  - Report to the President by the Emergency Board, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    To investigate unadjusted disputes between the Pennsylvania Railroad Company and certain of its employees represented by the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen
  - Report to the President by Emergency Board No. 61, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    Reconvened on August 23, 1948
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 10, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    Witness: LW Horning
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 11, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    Assignment studies
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 13, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    Negotiation of the firemen's eastern diesel agreement of August 13, 1943
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 14, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    Recommendation of 1943 Diesel Board compared with Eastern settlement agreement
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 20, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 21, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    Affidavit from HL Heinz Sr.
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 22, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    Safety
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 23, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    Summary of accidents reported by steam railways for the month of April 1949
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 24, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    Steam Railway Accidents Preliminary Summary from the Bureau of Transport Economics and Statistics, Washington
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 25, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    Monthly Comment on Transportation Statistics; July 1949
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 26, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    Time studies
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 27, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    Infractions of operations rules and instructions/requests for diesel assignments
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 29, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    Number of maintainers, diesel supervisors, etc. (witness: F.C. Wenk)
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 33, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    Report to the President by the Emergency Board created December 12, 1944 Under Section 10 of the Railway Labor Act
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 35, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 55)
    Witness: H.T. Clark
  - Third Diesel Case Carriers' Exhibit No. 36, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 56)
    Higher than standard rates - western territory